어지러운 전국 시대.
It is the turbulent Sengoku period.
카라쿠리인이 사는 지팡구국에서는 군웅할거하여 밤낮으로 접전이 계속되고
Warlords keep on fighting day and night over
Jipangu State, where Karakuri people live.
카라쿠리 무예가들도 승리와 영광을 꿈꾸며 맹렬히 싸우고 있었다.
Karakuri martial artists were sharpening their swords, dreaming of victory and honor.
그리고 지금, 카라쿠리 무예가 제일을 꿈꾸는 터무니없는 영웅이 탄생했다!
And now, a wild hero has arrived, seeking to be the number one Karakuri martial artist!
무사시 등장이오!
Musashi is here-dasu!
카라쿠리 검호전: 무사시 로드
Karakuri Kengouden
Musashi Road
(The Story of Karakuri Martial Artist: Road of Musashi)
사내는 언제나 세계 한가운데서
A man always dreams of the day
제일 강해질 날을
in the center of the world to become
아! 아! 꿈꿔라
AH! AH! the strongest
마음의 칼을 넓은 하늘로 번쩍 쳐들어
Raise the sword of your heart high to the wide sky
모험의 길의 막을 연다
Raise the curtain to the road of adventure
지팡구국을 떠도는 검호
A skilled swordsman roams on Jipangu State
그 이름은 카라쿠리인 무사시
His name is Musashi, a Karakuri man
격렬한 승부의 소리는
The sound of fierce duels
눈부신 인생
makes life dazzling
싸웠던 어제보다도 오늘 강해진다
Battles of yesterdays make you stronger today
무예! 이도류 무사시
Martial Arts! Dual Blade Musashi
내일은 빛난다
Tomorrow will be glorious
격렬한 승부의 소리는
The sound of fierce duels
눈부신 인생
makes life dazzling
싸우는 한껏 고요함과 함께
Fight the utmost with the stillness
무예! 이도류 무사시
Martial Arts! Dual Blade Musashi
미간이 반짝였다 무사시!!
His eyes shined! Musashi!
무사시 일행은 료마에게서 받은 정보로 메가톤성을 쫒아 세토 내해로 향한다.
According to the information by Ryoma, Musashi and others head to Seto Inland Sea to chase Megaton Castle.
그러나 도중에 들른 섬에서는 한조의 함정이 설치되어 있었다.
But at the island they stopped by, Hanzo's trap was installed.
잡히고 만 센히메. 이를 구출하고자 급히 달려간 일동.
Senhime was captured. People went to rescue her.
그러나 최후에는 오츠루의 활약으로 궁지에서 탈출할 수 있었다.
But at last, thanks to Otsuru, they managed to escape their crisis.
하늘과 땅의
신겐신이오
Shingenshin
of Sky and Ground
끔찍하게 당했구나, 도쿠간류.
You were beaten terribly, Dokuganryu.
이건 육도마왕 님. 면목이 없습니다.
Lord Rikudomaoh. I deeply apologize.
국왕의 삼종의 신기의 하나 성검을 아직도 손에 넣을 수 없었습니다.
We still couldn't retrieve the sacred sword, the last of the king's Three Sacred Treasures.
뭐, 됐다. 나도 이에야스의 힘을 너무 얕잡아보고 있었구나.
Well, good enough. I might have been underestimating Ieyasu.
설마! 노부나가 님입니까.
No way! Are you Mr. Nobunaga?
노부나가는 이미 죽었다. 여기에 있는 건 노부나가를 넘은 마인 육도마왕이다.
Nobunaga is already dead. Who's here is Rikudomaoh, the ultimate one far transcending Nobunaga.
어디에 갈 생각이냐.
Where are you going?
흥. 이에야스의 개자식.
Hmph. You must be one of Ieyasu's underlings.
반응이 있었으니 멀리는 못 갈 테다.
You won't make it so far now.
지루하오...
I'm bored-dasu...
좋잖아? 지루하다는 건 평화롭다는 의미니까.
Isn't it great? You're bored because it's peaceful now!
뭔 소리이오, 오츠루. 이러고 있을 동안에도 육도마왕은 지팡구국을 노리고 있소!
What are you saying-dasu, Otsuru? Rikudomaoh is still looking to rule over Jipangu State even meanwhile-dasu!
무사시 씨는 나하고 있는 것보다 싸우는 게 좋은 거네.
Mr. Musashi, you like fighting more than being with me!
아, 아니, 그럴 말을 할 생각은 아니었소, 그러니까 울지 마시오, 오츠루.
N- no, I didn't mean that-dasu. Please don't cry-dasu, Otsuru.
몰라, 몰라!
I don't know anymore!
어라라, 무사시가 여자아이 울렸다.
Oh, hey, look. Musashi made a girl cry.
안 돼, 안 될 거야.
That's no good. You won't make it.
코지로! 한 소리 해 주시오!
Kojirō! Say something-dasu!
공교롭게도 난 여자아이를 울려본 적이 없어서 말이지.
Unfortunately, I never made a girl cry before.
그것만은 알아 두어라.
You should know that at least.
정말! 다들 날 구박한다니까!
Really! You're all teasing me!
이렇게 될 줄 알았다면 진즉에 돌려보냈으면 좋았을 걸 그랬소.
Maybe I should send her back at the first place, if I knew this was going to happen-dasu.
무사시 씨 너무해!
You're cruel, Mr. Musashi!
알았어! 돌아가면 되잖아? 돌아가면!
I get it! I'll go back! Are you happy?
돌아갈 거야!
I'm going back!
오츠루, 어쩔 생각이오!
Otsuru, what are you trying to do-dasu!?
놔! 에도토피아까지 헤엄쳐서 돌아갈 거야!
Let me go! I'll swim my way back to Edotopia!
그런 게 가능할 리 없소! 도중에 빠져서 익사하오!
That's impossible-dasu! You'll drown to death in your way-dasu!
어라?
Huh?
으악! 익사체이오.
Wah! A drowned body-dasu!
아직 숨이 붙어 있어.
He's still alive.
어이, 대체 누구에게 당했냐. 어이!
Hey, who did this to you? Hey!
주, 주베 님께 어서 보고를. 육도마왕의 정체는 노부나가.
R- report this to Jūbē as soon as possible. The identitiy of Rikudomaoh is Nobunaga.
뭐? 노부나가?
What? Nobunaga?
료마 씨, 노부나가라니 누구이오?
Mr. Ryoma, who is Nobunaga-dasu?
내가 어릴 적에 들었던 건데, 그 옛날에 지팡구국 통일을 노리고 싸웠던 정말 유명한 무장이지.
I heard about him when I was young.
He was a military commander who fought for the unification of Jipangu State long time ago.
할아버지 말이야?
You mean, my grandpa?
그 공격은 대담하고 호쾌했지만, 자기 마음에 안 드는 것은
His attack was bold and stirring, but he is told that he killed everyone
여자 어린이 늙은이 가림없이 닥치는 대로 모조리 살해했다고 전해지는 무서운 자다.
whoever he didn't like, including women, children, and old people.
그렇지만 지팡구국 통일을 눈 앞에 두고 부하 미츠히데에게 배신당해 템플 혼노에서 죽었다고 한다.
(See: Honnō-ji incident)
But leaving the unification of Jipangu State right ahead of him,
he was betrayed by his subordinate Mitsuhide, and died at Temple Honno, according to what I heard.
그럼 그 노부나가라는 사람은 죽었소?
Then, is that Nobunaga guy dead-dasu?
아니, 분명 일단 몸을 숨기고 전력을 기르고 있었을 지도 모른다.
No, it's possible that he hid himself first and raised war capacity until now.
주베 님의 부하가 이런 곳에서 그런 중대한 정보를 알아냈다는 건...
If Mr. Jūbē's man found out an information so important like that at this place...
분명 이 주변에 노부나가의 본거지가 있는 것이.
then Nobunaga's base must be around here.
좋아! 슬슬 식량을 보급하면 좋겠다 하고 생각하던 참이었다.
Alright! This is a good time to replenish food supply.
일단 조사해 보자.
Let's investigate during that.
일단 가까운 항구로 향해라.
Head to the nearest port.
지금 들어온 정보에 의하면 시끄러운 파리 놈들이 이 성을 찾을 겸 주변의 항구에 정박한 모양이다.
Per the information we just received, it seems that noisy flies anchored to the nearest port, finding this castle as well.
알겠냐, 너희들! 함께 협력해서 이 성에 한 발짝도 가까이 오지 못하게 해라.
Listen, you two! Work together and do not let them approach this castle even for one step!
말씀드릴 게 있습니다만, 노부나가 님, 이런 놈하고 같이 일하지 않아도
I have one objection, Lord Nobunaga. I do not have to work with this guy.
고작 꼬맹이 한 점이나 두 점은 이 신겐이 쫒아버리는 걸 보아 주십시오.
Please watch I, Shingen, repealing a brat or two easily.
흥. 그건 내가 할 말이다. 이 붉은 카라쿠리 오뚝아!
Hmph, that's my line, you red Karakuri tumbler!
뭐야!? 이 번쩍이기나 하는 놈이!
What!? You're nothing more than shining!
둘 다 멈추어라!
Stop it, you two!
그들은 내 명령이 안 들리는 건가.
Are you suggesting that you do not understand my order?
다, 당치도 않은 말씀이십니다.
T- that's impossible.
그 무사시인가 하는 꼬맹이 놈들을 깔보면 안 된다. 단단히 명심해라.
You must not look down of that Musashi brats. Do not forget.
예!
Yessir!
와, 하이레그 입은 누나들이 잔뜩 있소!
There are so many girls wearing high-leg leotard-dasu!
오른쪽을 봐도,
So much on right!
왼쪽을 봐도!
So much on left!
그딴 태평한 소리 하고 있을 때냐!
This is not a time for such a thoughtless speech!
우리는 노부나가의 아지트를 찾으러 온 거야!
We're here to find the hideout of Nobunaga!
무사시 씨도 참, 언제 그렇게 호색해졌어?
Mr. Musashi, when did you became so lewd?
어? 그렇게 한번에 화내지 않아도 되오, 정말!
You don't have to be angry all at once-dasu! Really!
무사시. 우리는 몰래 적의 아지트를 찾고 있는 거야. 더 긴장해!
Musashi, we're here to find the hideout of our enemy. Be serious!
센짱, 그 모습이 긴장한 것이오?
Sen-chan, you call that serious-dasu?
당연하잖아! 적의 눈을 속이기 위한 변장이지!
Isn't it obvious? I disguised to fool the enemies!
그럼 난 바다 쪽으로 알아보러 갈게!
Then I'll go investigate the seaside!
우리도 변장하오?
Should we disguise, too-dasu?
그거 좋을지도!
That might be a good idea!
100관
(375kg)
100 kan
(375kg; 830lb)
(触らぬ神に祟りなし: 긁어 부스럼 만들지 말 것; 神를 女로 바꾸었음)
(触らぬ神に祟りなし: lit. Don't touch the gods, and you won't be harmed;
if it ain't broke, don't fix it; the line used 女(woman) instead of 神(god))
여자는 안 건드려야 탈이 없소!
Let sleeping womens lie!
동감.
Agreed.
오츠루 씨, 보이는 것과는 달리 성질이 거칠구나.
Ms. Otsuru is so bad-tempered, unlike how she looks...
지라이얀! 그 쪽에선 뭐 찾았소?
Jiraiyan! Did you figured something out on your side?
아니, 전혀!
No, not at all!
그럼 코지로는 어떻소?
Then, what about you-dasu, Kojirō?
발견했으면 이런 곳에서 빙수 따위나 먹고 있겠냐!
If I did, then would I be here, eating some snow cone?
그것도 그렇소!
Makes sense-dasu!
한 그릇 더!
One more dish!
그래도, 노부나가의 아지트라는 거, 대체 어디에 있을까?
Anyway, I wonder where would the hideout of Nobunaga at!
한 그릇 더!
One more dish!
어쩌면 그 밀정은 서쪽에서 해류에 휩쓸려 온 게 아닐까?
It's possible that spy is swept away by ocean current from west.
너희들, 그렇게 빨리 먹으면 머리가 띵 하고 아파진다!
You guys, if you eat that so fast, then your heads will go dull!
그래도 코지로는 너무 느긋하게 먹어서 얼음이 녹았소.
But Kojirō, yours has melt because you ate too slowly-dasu.
뭐야!?
What!?
아, 내 빙수가!
My snow cone!
-나, 5그릇째오!
-난 3번!
-난 3그릇째야!
-I'm having 5th dish-dasu!
-I'm 3rd!
-I'm having 3rd dish!
야, 무사시, 수박 가르기에 초대받았어! 따라와!
Hey, Musashi! We're invited to watermelon diving! Follow me!
알았소, 가오!
Alright, we'll go-dasu!
-아, 나도!
-나도!
-Me too!
왜 왔냐?
Why are you here?
주인! 빙수 수북하게 한 그릇 더.
Boss! One more dish of snow cone of large serving.
아, 무사시, 더 왼쪽이야, 왼쪽!
Hey, Musashi, a little bit to the left!
아니야, 오른쪽이야, 오른쪽!
No, it's right! Right!
어디이오!
Where is it-dasu!?
-왼쪽이야, 왼쪽!
-오른쪽이야, 무사시 씨!
-It's left! Left!
-It's right, Mr. Musashi!
좋아! 왼쪽이오!
Alright! Right then-dasu!
아, 안 돼!
No, that's not right!
그래, 쭉 가라!
Great! Go that way!
정말!
Really!
무사시 씨, 오른쪽이야!
Mr. Musashi, it's right!
그렇소, 나 오츠루를 믿소!
Right, I believe in Otsuru-dasu!
처음부터 그래 줬으면 좋았는데!
You should've done that at the first place!
미안, 미안!
Sorry, sorry!
그래, 조금만 왼쪽으로!
Yeah, a little bit to the left!
그래, 그래!
Right, right!
좋소!
Great!
어이, 기합 넣어 해라!
Hey, do it with full force!
가오!
I'm doing this-dasu!
힘 넣어서 해, 무사시!
Hit with all your might, Musashi!
수박 군, 각오하시오!
Watermelon, prepare yourself-dasu!
했소!
I did it!
왜 수박이 폭발하오...
Why would a watermelon explode-dasu?
무사시!
Musashi!
어? 너는?
Huh? Who're you?
기다리고 있었다, 무사시.
I was waiting for you, Musashi.
뭣이!?
What!?
너 보아하니 우리 아지트를 찾고 있는 것 같은데, 다 같이 가도 좋아.
It seems that you're looking for our hideout. You all can come with us.
어? 정말이오?
Huh? Really-dasu?
그래, 다만...
Yeah, but...
네 머리뿐이다.
your head only.
여러분은 위험하니까 어서 피난해 주세요!
It's dangerous here! Please take shelter!
뭣이!? 어떻게 된 거냐, 이건!
What!? What's going on here!?
이 해안 사람들은 모두 내 부하.
All the people on this beach are my subordinates.
자, 순순히 포기해라!
You'd better give up now!
난처하오.
This is bad-dasu.
늘 여름인 해수욕장에서 둘러싸인 무서운 함정에서 무사시 일행은 탈출할 수 있을까? 질풍노도의 후반을 기다려라!
Will they manage to escape from the fearful trap on the beach of everlasting summer? Wait for the stormy latter half!
카라쿠리 검호전 무사시 로드
Karakuri Kengouden: Musashi Road
이걸로 공훈은 내 것이다! 그 목, 쳐 주겠다!
The exploits are mine by this! Let me break your neck!
멈춰라!
Stop!
켄신! 네가 공훈을 독차지하게는 못 둔다!
Kenshin! I cannot let you take all the exploits!
어떻게 된 일이오?
What's going on-dasu?
자, 이 틈에!
This is our chance!
아, 내 공훈이!
My exploits!
다들! 공훈은 우리 것이다! 쫒아라, 쫒아!
Everyone! The exploits are ours! Chase them, chase!
네놈, 공훈을 빼앗을 셈이냐!
Are you going to steal all the exploits!?
알고 있으면 묻지 마라!
Don't ask what you know!
달아나게 두지 마라! 무사시는 우리 손으로 잡는다!
Don't let them get away! We'll get Musashi with our own hands!
예!
Yessir!
앞으로 한 발짝도 못 걷겠어.
I can't walk anymore.
여기까지 오면 이젠 괜찮을 것이오.
We should be fine, since we came pretty far-dasu.
그래도, 해수욕장에 있던 게 모두 적이었다니 놀랐어, 정말!
But still, the fact that everyone at the beach was enemy was surprising!
그런 무서운 함정을 깔아 둔 부하가 있다니.
To have subordinates who are capable of installing a fearful trap like that...
노부나가라는 자, 꽤나 하는 무장이구나.
that Nobunaga is pretty capable.
찾아냈군, 공훈의 머리!
I finally found the heads of achievement!
좋아! 나도!
Alright! Me too!
어라?
Huh?
아, 그래, 내 껀 변형 안 했지.
Oh, right. Mine didn't change.
누, 누구냐!
W- who's there!?
저것들은 내 공훈이다! 순순히 손떼라!
They are my achievements! Get your hands off them!
케, 켄신! 내 행복을 방해하지 마라!
K- Kenshin! Do not interrupt my happiness!
네놈들이야말로 내 출세를 방해하지 마라!
You don't interrupt my success!
뭔 소리냐! 너야말로 내 것을 빼앗지 마라!
What are you saying? You don't steal what's mine!
애초에 내가 손을 댔다! 각오해라!
I was dealing with them at the first place! Prepare yourself!
젠장, 뭔 짓이냐!
Damn! What are you doing!?
방해는 소용 없다!
You won't get in my way!
고맙소, 코지로!
Thank you, Kojirō!
무사시. 센히메 님을 데리고 달아나라!
Musashi. Take Senhime to somewhere safe!
쉽소!
That's easy-dasu!
자, 센짱!
Now, Sen-chan!
무사시 씨, 나도 갈래!
Mr. Musashi, let me go, too!
자, 오츠루는 우리하고 같이!
Otsuru, you can follow us!
그래도 무사시가 센히메 님하고 둘이서만 있게 되어 버리잖아!
But that means Musashi is left with Senhime by two!
걱정할 필요 없습니다! 저렇게 보여도 무사시는 유사시에는 믿음직한 놈입니다.
There's nothing to worry! He doesn't look so, but he actually is dependable in the time of need.
아니야!
You're wrong!
어?
What?
어쨌든 여긴!
Anyway, this place is...
어! 너희 두목이 위험하다!
Hey! Your bosses are in danger!
-켄신 님!
-신겐 님!
-Lord Kenshin!
-Lord Shingen!
자, 이 틈에!
Now's our chance!
위험했어.
That was close.
그렇소. 오츠루 괜찮을지...
Right. I wonder if Otsuru's fine-dasu...
무사시, 정말 오츠루 좋아하는구나?
Musashi, you truly like Otsuru, don't you?
아니, 그건, 결혼하자고 맹새했으니까...
Well, that's... we made an oath to marry-dasu...
안심했더니 왠지 으스스 추워졌어!
Now that I'm relieved, it became chilly!
무사시! 뭐라도 해 봐!
Musashi! Do something!
그건 안 좋소. 뭔가 입을 게...
That's not good-dasu. Something to wear...
이런 곳에는...
There's no way one would be here...
좋겠네, 오츠루는.
I envy Otsuru.
그렇소!
Right!
뭐 해, 무사시?
What are you doing, Musashi?
이걸 이렇고 이렇게...
Do this, do that, and...
무사시?
Musashi?
이렇게!
Do this!
자!
Look!
볼품은 없지만 추위는 일단 피할 수 있소.
It's unsightly, but it'll help you deal with the coldness-dasu.
무사시 다정하구나?
Musashi, you're really gentle.
어?
Huh?
오츠루가 무사시를 좋아하는 것도 알 거 같아.
I think I understand why would Otsuru like you.
아니, 센짱도 참! 그런 소리를 해서 날 놀리오...
No, Sen-chan, you're ridiculing me with that-dasu!
무사시 씨!
Mr. Musashi!
오츠루!
Otsuru!
무사시! 무사했냐!
Musashi! You're safe!
코지로! 지라이얀! 이야, 잘 되었소! 오츠루도 무사해서 무엇보다도!
Kojirō! Jiraiyan! What a relief-dasu! Otsuru's safe, too-
오츠루!
Otsuru!
왜, 왜 화났소?
W- why are you angry-dasu?
흥!
Hmph!
자, 서둘러서 여기서 도망치자. 항구로 가면 료마 씨가 있으니.
Let's hurry our way back to the port. Mr. Ryoma is waiting for us.
좋아!
Right!
끈질긴 놈들!
They're so persistent!
코지로!
Kojirō!
우리 공훈은 전방에 있다!
Our achievements are in our front!
공훈을 켄신에게 빼앗길 수 없다!
Don't let Kenshin take our achievements!
네이놈, 신겐! 같은 편에 쏘다니 정신이 나갔나!
Shingen, you bastard! Are you out of mind, to shoot at ally!?
흥! 공훈은 딴 자가 이기는 것. 다들 가라!
Hmph! The one to obtain the achievement wins! Everyone, go!
또 지들끼리 싸우기 시작했소.
They started to fight themselves again-dasu.
멍청한 놈들이다. 자, 이 틈에!
How stupid of them. This is our chance!
달아날 쏘냐!
You won't get away from this!
우리는 아저씨들 출세의 도구가 아니오!
We are not the tools for success of you old men-dasu!
공훈은 내 것이다!
The achievement is mine!
방해 마라! 이건 내 것이다!
Do not interrupt! This is mine!
비검 츠바메가에시!
Secret Sword Tsubamegaeshi!
네가 방해하니까 찬스를 놓쳤잖아!
Your interrupt made me miss the chance!
뭣이!? 내 탓 마라!
What!? Don't blame me!
이천일류 섬광검!
Nitenichiryu: Flash Sword!
자, 봐라! 네가 꼬박꼬박 끼어드니까 막 당하고 있잖아!
Look for yourself! Your continuous interruption is allowing them chances!
에잇, 이대로는 안 되겠다!
Damn, this won't get us anymore!
일단 힘을 모으는 것으로 할까!
We should combine our powers for now!
어쩔 수 없다!
Sure!
천지합체!
Sky Ground Fusion!
뭐, 뭣이오!?
W- what-dasu!?
으앗! 뭣이오, 이 괴물은!
Woah! What is that monster-dasu?
괴물이 아니다! 이건 우리의 최종 체형, 신겐신이다!
We are not a monster! This is our ultimate form, Shingenshin!
신겐신? 앞에서 읽어도 신겐신, 뒤에서 읽어도 신겐신.
Shingenshin? It's Shingenshin when I read from beginning, and it's Shingenshin again when I read from back.
그딴 느긋한 거 생각하고 있을 때냐!
Is it time to think about such an useless thing!?
아, 그랬소.
You're right-dasu.
내 이도류를 맛보시오!
Taste the wrath of my dual blades-dasu!
그 쪽이 이도류라면 우린 사도류다!
If you call that dual blades, then we're quadruple blades!
무슨! 4개나 쓰다니 비겁하오!
What!? Using four is cowardly-dasu!
너라고 해도 두 개나 쓰고 있잖냐?
Aren't you using multiple swords already?
젠장!
Damn!
아이고, 발이!
My legs!
무사시!
Musashi!
코지로! 괜찮소?
Kojirō! Are you okay-dasu?
그래, 어떻게든... 아야!
Yeah, somehow... ouch!
애초에 합체했으면 공훈을 빼앗을 필요도 없었구나.
If we combined at the first place, we wouldn't even have to steal achievements.
자, 그 목은 가져가겠다, 무사시, 코지로!
I'll take your necks, Musashi and Kojirō!
코지로, 난 냅두고 어서 달아나시오!
Kojirō, leave me here, and run away immediately-dasu!
멍청아! 그게 가능할 것 같냐!
You idiot! Do you think I can do that?
단지 칼을 들 수 있을 힘이 이 손에 있기만 하다면...
Only if I had powers to raise my sword...
자, 코지로! 이 위에 칼을 올리시오! 칼은 내가 받치오!
Kojirō, put your sword on these-dasu! I'll hold up the sword-dasu!
무사시! 알겠다!
Musashi! Got it!
언제 포기할 지 모르는 놈들!
Know when to give up!
각오해라!
Prepare yourself!
필살! 봉황검!
Special Technique Phoenix Sword!
코지로!
Kojirō!
자, 이 틈에!
Ride on!
에잇, 젠장! 기억해 둬라!
Damn it! Remember this!
이건 꽤나 어려웠소.
That was terrible-dasu.
그래, 적의 아지트는 느긋히 찾고 일단 몸을 회복해야지.
Yes. We can find the enemy's hideout later; your bodies come first.
잘 됐어. 나, 무사시 씨, 무사시 씨가 죽으면...
What a relief. I was worried what if Mr. Musashi dies...
오츠루, 걱정을 끼쳐서 미안했소! 그래도 나 불사신이오!
Otsuru, sorry for making you worry-dasu! But I'm invincible-dasu!
무사시 씨!
Mr. Musashi!
다리, 다리, 다리 밟지 마시오, 다리, 다리, 다리!
My leg! My leg! Don't step on my leg! My leg!
신겐신의 공격은 무사시와 코지로의 우정 파워로 쫓아낼 수 있었다.
Musashi and Kojirō's friendship power has managed to repeal the attack of Shingenshin.
그러나 적의 무서운 공격력을 안 무사시 일행의 가슴에는 불안이 남았다.
But now they know the fearsome attacking potential of the enemy, an anxiety remains in their hearts.
싸움의 넓은 바다는 지금 크게 거칠어지려 한다.
The wide ocean of battle is about to become violent.
싸우고 맞았어
I fought and I got beaten
코피 쓩이야 랑데부
Nosebleed drips rendezvous
나도 지지 않으려 한발!
I can't lose, so take my blow!
핀치 펀치로 대역전
Pinch! Punch! I won by reversal
다음 시간 즐거운
Next is delightful lunchtime
급식일 텐데
But it's not delightful today
선생님의 벼락이
The thunder of my teacher
나한테만 떨어져 왔어
only hit me and nobody else
사정을 말해도
I tried to explain
들어주지 않는 채
But he won't listen
어떻게 해도 역시
Now whatever I do
눈물이 나오고 말아
I end up crying
울면서 밥먹으면
Don't cry when you eat, or
완전 맛없어
it tastes totally bad
울면서 밥먹으면
Don't cry when you eat, or
완전 맛없어
it tastes totally bad
울면서 밥먹으면
Don't cry when you eat, or
완전 맛없어
it tastes totally bad
울면서 밥먹으면
Don't cry when you eat, or
왠지 안타까워
you'll feel downhearted
우주인이 숨겨둔 갑옷이 있다는 이야기를 듣고 우리는 곧장 그곳으로 향하오.
Hearing that there are armors hidden by aliens, we're heading to the place right away-dasu.
왜냐면, 이대로는 그 한조에게 이길 수 있을 리가 없기 때문이오.
That's because it's impossible for us to defeat that Hanzo at this rate-dasu.
그래도 간단하게는 손에 안 들어오오. 물에 빠질 뻔했다던지, 계단에서 떨어진다던지.
But it's difficult to claim them-dasu. We almost drown in waters, and we fell from stairs.
고난의 길을 몇만 리! 아니, 그 정도는 아닐 것이오.
Thousands of ris of the road of pain! Well, not that much, but still-dasu!
다음 이야기! 요염한 모습 카라쿠리 변화이오
Next Story! Charming Outlook Karakuri Shift
질풍노도의 우주인이오!
It's stormy aliens-dasu!
다음 이야기
요염한 모습
카라쿠리 변화이오
기대하세요!
Next Episode
Charming Outlook
Karakuri Shift
Look forwards for it!